我最棒的一次偶遇明星经验
What was my best brush with celebrity?
这真是个好问题
Oh, this is such a good one.
有次我在洗车店看到了杰克·尼科尔森
One time I saw Jack Nicholson at the car wash.
我简直不想再说了
I can't go through this again.
杰克·尼科尔森不会开一辆贴着
Jack Nicholson does not drive a Hyundai Odyssey
"宗教共存"的现代奥德赛 小卡
with a Co-Exist bumper sticker, Cam.
在橱柜行业干了那么多年
Being in the closet business,
我遇到过许多明星
I met a lot of famous people.
我不能提名字
I can't name names,
就这么说吧 那人是老大
but let's just say it's someone who's the boss.
你遇到布鲁斯·斯普林斯汀吗
You met Bruce Springsteen?
-不 是托尼·丹扎 -电视剧里的吗
- No, Tony Danza. - Oh, from the TV show?
那部剧女主才是老大
Nah, she was the boss.
个人见解不同啦
It's open to interpretation.
我在商场看见了圣诞老人
I saw Santa Claus at the mall.
《不知情的卡斯尔小姐》
"The Unwitting Miss Castle."
讲的是什么
What's that about?
讲的是不同时代中
It's about three persecuted women
三个被迫害的女人
in different time periods,
或者是一个特别倒霉的时间旅行者
or one time traveler with incredibly bad luck.
我不知道是哪个
I don't know which.
我莫名其妙加入了
Somehow, I was able to join
一个非常排外的读书俱乐部
a very exclusive book club
里面都是超高智商的女人
filled with the most intelligent women.
我总是无法令她们感到惊艳
I can never seem to impress them.
她们会用"枯苗望雨"这种高级词
They use words like "Sanguine."
我不想看起来像是个傻瓜 所以我也用
I don't want to look like an idiot, so I use it, too.
这是不是你听到过的最"枯苗望雨"的东西
Isn't that the most sanguine thing you ever heard?
你用错了
You're not using it right.
同一章我都读了八次了
I've read the same chapter eight times --
还是不懂
still don't get it.
就说"这反映了社会现状"
Just say, "It holds a mirror up to society."
你会得个C 顺利脱身
You'll get your "C" and get out of there.
-早上好 -嗨
- Good morning. - Hi.
这年轻人是谁
Who's that young thing?
怎么打扮成这样 像电视剧的人一样犀利啊
Wow, what's up with the outfit, Mod Squad?
是啊 我要...
Oh, yeah, I'm, uh...
我要带人看房
I'm showing a house to someone.
我不想说是谁
I'd rather not say who it is.
我完全理解
I totally get that.
是酷玩乐队的主唱克里斯·马汀
It's Chris Martin from Coldplay.
-拜托 真的吗 -不是什么大事啦
- Come on, really? - It's not a big deal.
说这话的人昨晚花了大半晚上时间
Says the man who spent most of last night
往牛仔裤上缝花
sewing that flower onto his jeans.
好吧 这真的是件大事
Okay, it's a really big deal.
我要跟一个唱出我感受的歌手见面了
I'm meeting the man who sings how I feel.
是啊 他的音乐非常"枯苗望雨"
Yes, his music is so sanguine.
比上次强
Eh, closer.
我从来都不是很喜欢酷玩乐队
Never been a big Coldplay guy.
我更喜欢嘻哈 死亡金属
I'm more into hip-hop, death metal,
《小美人鱼》
"Little Mermaid."
那电影对我小时候影响好大啊
That one really imprinted on me back in the day.
我肚子很难受
My stomach feels weird.
你也许只是紧张
You're probably just nervous.
也许你需要有人陪你去
Ooh, maybe you need someone to come with you.
不要 他是去买房的 不是谈论音乐的
No, he's there to buy a house, not talk about music,
所以我压根都不会提
which is why I'm not even gonna mention
我也是歌曲作家
that I'm a songwriter, too.
你就写了一首歌
Oh, you wrote one song.
歌里有我想说的一切了
I said everything I had to say.
房地产经纪人的故事
About a realtor.
是关于人生
It was about life!
难怪读书俱乐部的人嘲笑你
This is why they mock you at book club.
我可以聊聊某一次
Oh, here's a brush with celebrity
和明星的偶遇
I can actually talk about.
去年夏天 我被要求
Last summer, I was called upon
参与最美式的传统
to participate in the most American of traditions --
摆脱陪审团的职责
getting out of jury duty.
您有任何跟执法机构接触的经验吗
Do you have any experience with law enforcement?
多了去了
Big time.
我不信任警察
I-I don't trust, uh, cops.
而且我鄙视被抢劫的人
Also, I despise robbery victims.
他们才是真正的罪犯
They're the real criminals
占用了我们的审判系统
for clogging up our court system.
想得美 3号陪审员
Nice try, Juror 3.
那么经济困难呢
What about economic hardship?
上次我没去工作时
The last time I missed work,
加州橱柜市场都崩溃了
the California closet market collapsed.
有人认为那导致了洛杉矶暴动
Some people think that caused the L.A. Riot.
看来我该收声了
I must be done talking.
我要生了
I'm going into labor.
女士 一切都会没事的
Ma'am, Ma'am, everything's gonna be all right.
法警 帮助一下11号陪审员
Bailiff, help Juror 11 with anything she needs,
叫下一位替换陪审员
and bring in the next alternate.
作为她无痛分娩法的教练
Uh, as her Lamaze coach,
我想我该去走廊...
I think I should probably be out in the hall wi--
特里·布拉德肖
Terry Bradshaw.
我爱特里·布拉德肖
I love Terry Bradshaw!
11号陪审员 有什么原因会阻止你
Juror 11, is there anything that might prevent you
有效地履行陪审团义务吗
from serving effectively on this jury?
日程没有冲突 法官大人
No scheduling conflicts, Your Honor.
然而我现在
However, I am going through
正经历一段困难的时期
kind of a rough patch right now.
我失去了我死党
You see, I lost my best friend.
还是他刚找到了一位新死党
Or did he just find one?
但我很高兴履行义务
But I'm happy to serve.
我相信美国司法制度
I believe in the American legal system,
靠的就是团队合作
and I believe it's all about teamwork.
真是个"触地得分"的好答案啊 冠军
That's a touchdown of an answer, champ.
这位女士
Uh, this lady here...
我决定也当陪审员
put me down for that.
你准备好接受正义制裁了吗
Are you ready for some justice?
天啊
Oh, my God.
怎么了 有明星吗
What? A celebrity?
-是山姆·安威尔马克 -谁
- It's Sam Anvilmaker. - Who?
他写了《遗忘者和被遗忘者》
He wrote "The Forgetters and the Forgotten"?
《美国式闹剧》
"Farce, American Style"?
《读这本书就滚蛋》
"Screw You For Reading This"?
"这到底什么情况"
What the hell is happening?
对 这也是他写的
Yes, that one, too!
他是我最喜欢的编剧
He's my favorite playwright.
你为什么不过去
Why don't you go over
告诉他你是他粉丝
and tell him that you're a fan?
也许他会给你一些建议
Maybe he can give you some advice.
不不 我不想打扰他
No, no, I wouldn't want to bother him.
他不喜欢被打扰是出了名的
He's notoriously private.
他在蒙大纳某处的一棵
He writes in a hollowed-out tree
挖空的树干里头写作
somewhere in Montana.
别紧张
Don't be nervous.
我就是感觉这样不太好
It just doesn't feel right.
曼尼 如果有人像你这么喜欢我的作品
Manny, if somebody admired my work as much as this,
我会很想知道的
I would like to know.
-去吧 -好吧
- Go. - Okay.
那我过去了
Here we go.
-打扰一下 安威尔马克先生 -让我猜猜
- Uh, excuse me, Mr. Anvilmaker? - Let me guess --
我是你想成为编剧的原因
I'm the reason you want to be a writer.
是的 没错
Yeah, actually.
您的第一部剧改变了我对...
Your first play changed the way that I looked at --
听我说 孩子
Look, listen, kid.
我不是来这里收集
I'm not here to collect panties
写着电话号码的内裤的
with phone numbers on them.
我是来这里体验活着的那种
I'm here to experience the cold absurdity
冷漠荒诞感
that is being alive.
找别人崇拜去吧
So go and find someone else to venerate.
很抱歉打扰你了
Oh, uh... Sorry for bothering you.
给你一条写作小窍门
Here's a writing tip --
让我看到你真为打扰我而感到抱歉
show me you're sorry for bothering me.
而不是光动嘴皮子
Don't tell me.
好了 来为这两个
Okay, let's take a picture
新交的死党拍张合影
of the two new best friends.
快靠近点儿
Come together.
我就不该离开我的树
I should never have left my tree.
我还在我们的干洗店看到了
And then, I saw Daniel Day-Lewis
影帝丹尼尔·戴·路易斯
at our dry cleaner.
不是他 真不是
Not him. No.
我们真的看到名人是在
Uh, the time we actually saw a celebrity
去年十二月
was last December
我们去买园艺用品的时候
when we were shopping for gardening supplies.
我永远不会忘记影帝演的林肯总统
I'll never forget the feeling of having Lincoln
直勾勾地看着我的眼睛 然后说
look directly into my eyes and saying,
"烧烤酱洗不掉"时候的感觉
"We couldn't get the barbecue sauce out."
我们不需要一人有一副
We both don't need a pair.
我们可以共用啊
We can just share these.
如果我想要我自己的呢
And what if I want my own?
我们什么东西都共用啊
We share everything.
我们共用一把牙刷
We share a toothbrush.
-有吗 -我的...我的天哪
- We do? Oh... - Oh, my -- Oh, my gosh.
那个主持我们非常喜欢的
Hm? There's the guy who hosts
家居大改造节目的家伙在那里
that home makeover show we love so much.
-什么 在哪儿 -斯科特·亨特
- What? Where? - It's Scott Hunter.
斯科特·亨特在那里
Scott Hunter is right over there.
每一周 斯科特·亨特
Every week, Scott Hunter,
《花您一点时间》的主持人
the host of "I Beg Your Garden,"
会在家居店挑选不知情的两口子
selects an unsuspecting couple at a home store.
对 他会拍他们的肩膀 然后说
Yeah, he taps them on the shoulder and says,
"花您一点时间"
"I beg your garden."
什么 我的天啊 真的假的
What?! Oh, my God! I can't believe it!
每次都这样
That's how it goes every time.
每次都是
Every time.
-摄像机在哪里 -我知道
- Where are the cameras? - I know.
要是我今天穿得更艳丽一点就好了
I wish I would've worn something more colorful.
你知道吗
Okay, you know what?
我们一定要上节目
We have to get on the show.
你能想象我们后院被大改造吗
Can you imagine a backyard makeover,
他会怎么改造我们的后院呢
what he would do with ours?
没错 是三个字的
Yeah, one word, three syllables,
开头是"小" 结尾是"凉亭"
starts with "Gah," ends with "zebo."
小凉亭
Gazebo.
-我爱死小凉亭了 -我也是
- I love gazebos. - I do, too!
一开始想这个
Now that I'm thinking about it,
我就非得要一个了
I have to have one.
-天哪 -我们工作这么辛苦
- Oh, my gosh. - Wait, we work hard.
当然有权在后院
We deserve to stand in the shade
-离草皮几英寸的地方乘凉 -就是
- a few inches off the ground. - Yeah.
这样吧
Okay, you know what?
-我们这就过去让他拍我们肩膀 -好
- Let's go get tapped. - Okay.
那是什么东西
Hm, what's over here?
不知道 天啊 米奇尔 你喜欢这个花盆吗
I don't know. Oh, my gosh, Mitchell, do you like this planter?
把这放在我们那个
It would go great
荒芜老气得掉渣的后院里一定不错
in our hopelessly outdated and neglected backyard.
你喜欢我就喜欢
Well, I love it if you love it.
那你觉得这些铺路材料怎么样
And what do you think of these pavers?
我觉得那会跟我们
Oh, I think they go great with that gazebo
梦寐以求的小凉亭很搭的
we've always dreamed of having.
拉倒吧 他走了
Oh, forget it. He's gone.
我们做错什么了 我们很讨喜啊
W-What did we do wrong? We were pleasant.
你猜怎么着 可能是我们太讨喜了
You know what? Maybe we were too nice.
上这些节目的小两口总是各种闹矛盾
Couples on those shows always have conflict.
-我们也是啊 -对啊
- So do we. - Yeah.
我们有多久没有达成一致过了
When's the last time we agreed on anything.
我们永远在斗嘴啊
We -- We're constantly bickering.
是啊 虽然斗嘴有时会反应出更深层的东西
I know, sometimes it reveals something deeper,
但并不总是如此
but not always.
来
You know what?
我们去向他展示一下我们
Let's go show him our delightful brand
毒舌得可爱的一面吧
of bitchy friction.
跟我想的完全一样
I was thinking the exact same thing.
-别总是跟我心有灵犀啊 -抱歉抱歉
- Stop seeing eye-to-eye with me. - Sorry, sorry.
我们去找他 然后好好大吵一架
Let's go find him and drum up an argument.
这主意太赞了
Yeah, terrific idea.
我不是故意跟你有默契的
I'm not doing it on purpose.
我只是...
I'm just...
我这是怎么了
What is going on?
我的...
My gro --
简直是噩梦
This was a nightmare.
我马上就要见到我的英雄
I was about to meet my hero,
可我那个地方却莫名疼得要死
and I was experiencing this bizarre pain in --
就是 下面那个地方
in my...nether region.
等等 我是个成年男性
Wait, I'm a grown man.
我应该不羞于直呼其名 我左边的蛋袋
I should be able to say it -- my left bean bag --
我又没说出口
did it again.
我的金玉蛋...
My tersticle --
我想我没办法说得更直接了
That's as close as I think I'm gonna get.
有人吗
Hello?
欢迎欢迎欢迎
Welcome, welcome, welcome.
-菲尔 -我是克里斯
- Phil. - Hey, I'm Chris.
-你怎么了 -没怎么
- Hey, what's wrong? - Oh, nothing.
你以为我本人会更帅些
You thought I'd be better looking.
人们总这么以为 因为乐队其他人
People think that because the rest of the band
-都长得跟霍比特人似的 -不不不
- look like hobbits. - No, no, no.
只是 我只是有点...
It's -- It's a little --
我喜欢你的花牛仔裤
I love your flower jeans.
你在哪买的
Where did you get those?
从商店买的
They're from a store.
特别有我的风格 特别有我的风格
Well, they're very me. They're very me.
你还记得店名吗
Do you remember the name of the store?
其实是我自己绣的
Actually, I embroidered them myself.
真了不起
Impressive.
等你准备好后
When you're ready for it,
你找件T恤 穿在长袖上衣外面
you get a T-shirt, you put it on top of a long-sleeve,
这样大家就知道你有不止一件上衣了
then it lets everybody know you own multiple shirts.
真厉害
Impressive.
伙计 我们要不要这就开搞
So, mate, shall we have a trod-about?
我受宠若惊
I'm flattered.
但我觉得我们还是专业点
I'd rather just keep it professional,
开始看房子吧
have a walk around.
我不是那个意思
Oh, that's not what...I...meant...
特里形单影只坐在那里
Terry was just sitting there by himself
因为人们总是不敢去和最漂亮的姑娘搭讪
because everybody's always afraid to talk to the prettiest girl,
除了这位
except this guy.
自信是关键
It's all about confidence.
打扰一下 布...
Excuse me, Mr. --
打扰一下 布拉德肖先生
Excuse me, Mr. Bradshaw.
杰·普里契特 三号陪审员
Jay Pritchett, juror number 3.
特里 叫我特里就行
Terry. Call me Terry.
-你好吗 特里 -挺好的 你呢
- How you doing, Terry? - Hi. Good. You?
关于这起抢劫案
Hey, this robbery case, huh?
我知道我们对案情还没有全面了解
Now, I know we don't have all the facts yet,
但我觉得我可能下不了决心
but I think it might be hard for me
让劫匪[钢人队]进监狱
to lock up a..."Steeler."
希望我没用力过猛
I try to keep it light.
你介意我坐下吗
You might if I join you?
不不不 这是自由的国家 坐
No, no, no, free country. Sit down.
他同意了
He said "Yes"!
七十年代的橄榄球赛要精彩多了
The '70s, it was a better game.
你们无所不能 进攻 防守
You guys did everything -- offense, defense.
你有次是不是还在赛前给场地除草来着
Didn't I see you mow the field one night before the game?
你知道我的钱就是靠除草赚来的吗
You know, that's how I made my money?
我真不敢相信
I can't actually believe
我在和特里·布拉德肖一起吃午餐
that I'm having lunch with Terry Bradshaw.
从橄榄球球星
I mean, from football fame
到乡村音乐明星到著名演员
to country music stardom to big-screen idol.
《横冲直撞斗飞车》续集
"Smokey and the Bandit II."
演自己 真的是项挑战
Now that was a challenge. To play yourself,
特别不好演
that can be kind of tricky.
我认为整部戏焦点都到你身上了
I thought you stole the movies?
别夸我了 你人太好了
Ah, stop that. You're too kind.
我也不是做什么成什么的
You know, not everything I touch turns to gold.
我这辈子也有过不少失误
I mean, I've had my share of missteps along the way.
是啊 例如《赖家王老五》 对吧
Well, right, like "Failure to Launch," right?
-什么 -你是该不好意思
- Sorry? - You should be.
那电影太差劲了
I mean, that thing was a real stinker.
我偏偏很为那部电影自豪
I happen to be proud of that movie.
那是我演得最好的电影之一
I mean, that's some of the best work I've ever done.
你演得当然很好 没错
No, you were good, yeah.
但演得好不好都没关系 反正没人看
But, I mean, don't worry about it. Nobody saw it.
那好
Yeah, well.
我想我们该回庭上了
Guess it's about time we get on back in, huh?
明天这时候再见
Same time tomorrow.
我日程表上全是空挡
Hey, I'm wide open.
像玩橄榄球时有空挡一样
Like in football.
没人能对我儿子那么说话
Nobody speaks to my son like that.
不 妈 妈 妈
No, no, Mom, Mom, Mom.
求你别过去大闹一场让我更丢人
Please don't get up and make a scene and embarrass me more.
我求你了
I'm begging you.
好 但你没必要堵住我吧
Okay, but you don't have to block me in.
我又不是疯婆子
I am not crazy.
你们都以为我是个冲动的拉丁女人
I am not the hot-headed Latina
但我不是那样的
that you all make me out to be.
你给儿童足球裁判寄过一颗牛心
You sent a cow heart to a children's soccer referee.
曼尼 不然我还能怎么警告他
Manny, what else was I supposed to do?
刚刚那一幕也是好事
Look, what happened was a good thing.
他在教我想做个艺术家
He was teaching me the focus required
就要有这种专注力
to live the life of an artist,
那是宝贵的一课 我会珍惜一辈子的
and that is a very valuable lesson that I'll cherish forever.
好吧宝贝 如果你开心我就开心
Okay, Papi, if you're happy, then I'm happy.
不如你挑份甜点吧
Why don't you pick your dessert?
我不介意来块杏仁饼干
I wouldn't say no to an almond cookie
一杯浓缩咖啡
and an espresso and...
你已经不在了 是不是
And you're gone, aren't you?
-亲爱的 再给我来份 -闭嘴
- Honey, I'll take another -- - Shut up.
那是我儿子
That's my son over there.
他对你赤诚相待
He opened his beautiful soul to you,
赞美你 向你寻求建议
to praise you, to get some advice from you,
你却对他这么刻薄
and you were mean to him?
拜托 我们都知道你这态度
Come on, we both know that your attitude
只是一种防卫机制
is just a defense mechanism
保护你那小得可怜的自我
to protect the tiny, little ego
不愿承认事实
from the truth --
事实就是你根本不配任何赞美
that you don't deserve any praise,
你是个骗子
that you're a fraud,
一个无足轻重的大胖子而已
that you're just a big, fat nobody.
所有男人都有一样的软肋
All men break the same.
这是什么鬼 这是什么意思
What's happening? What is all this?
-去下一个货架通道 -行
- Go up the next aisle. - Okay.
天啊
Oh, God,
我爱死我们新挑的地砖颜色了
I'm loving these new pavers we picked.
其实我又有点犹豫了
You know what, I'm starting to have second thoughts.
拜托
Oh, no, this isn't gonna be
我们不是又要开始吵了吧
another conflict between us, is it?
我的天 我可不想再和你吵了
Oh, gosh, I don't want another conflict.
你不会真的想买
Okay, you're -- you're not actually putting
这块再生木件吧
a reclaimed wood piece in our cart, are you?
说得好 说得好
That's great, that's great.
不 "再生木材美学"
No, the whole "reclaimed wood aesthetic"
是对谷仓文化的侮辱性剽窃
is an insulting appropriation of barn culture.
我是认真的
No, I'm being serious.
就像麦当娜穿工装裤的效果
It's like when Madonna wore overalls!
-太棒 -米奇尔 快拿走我不想要
- You're good. - Mitchell, take it out. I don't want it.
我觉得挺好看的
I think it's pretty.
我觉得这挺冒犯人的
I think it's pretty offensive.
控制一下你的情绪
Okay, rein it in.
看啊 修道院院长
Oh, there she is, Mother Superior.
够了 脸皮薄星人
Okay, Rumple-thinskin.
我不管了 我才不要吵
Okay, you know what? I don't need this.
我现在就去车里等着
I'm just gonna go wait in the car.
很好 逃走吧
Perfect, yeah, run away.
只是告诉你一下 我喜欢谷仓木
And just FYI, the reason I like barn wood
是因为它让我想到你
is 'cause it reminds me of you.
-真的吗 -真的
- Really? - Yeah.
我知道你有时候会很想家
I mean I-I know that you get homesick sometimes,
我就想给家里增添一点
and I-I want to bring
一点乡村的气息
a little, you know, country into our house.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不是有意要惹你生气的
Didn't mean to offend you.
我没生气
Oh, you didn't offend me.
我只是像你说的太玻璃心了
I'm just being oversensitive like you said.
我也是又开始骄傲自大了
I'm just being my normal snooty self.
真不知道你是怎么一直忍让我的
I don't -- I don't know how you put up with me.
是我不知道你怎么能一直忍我
I don't know how you put up with me.
我知道
I do.
不好意思
Excuse me.
-什么事 -怎么了 你好啊
- Oh. Yes? - Oh, yes? Hi.
我就是想借过一下
I just need to get by.
-行 -没问题
- Okay. - Okay.
他没有说那句话
He didn't say it.
他没说
最后就是 这里尽览全城美景
And last, but not least, the city at your feet.
我还是挺吃惊的
Yeah. I'm still kind of flabbergasted
这里竟然没有泡沫机
that there's no bubble machine.
没关系 我可以自己装一个
It's okay. I can install my own.
-你在鄙视我吗 -没有
- Oh, you're judging me? - No, no.
可能你是对的
Maybe you're right.
我可能的确越来越不食人间烟火了
Maybe I am losing touch with who I am.
人生只需要一把三弦吉他和一张床垫
All I really need is three chords and a mattress.
还有我的主厨就行了
And my chef.
菲尔 你怎么了
Uh, hey, Phil, what's happening here?
-拜托别加重 -菲尔
- Oh, not too much. - Phil?
我的天 你脸都憋黄了
Oh, my God, you've gone all yellow.
和你的歌名一样
That's like your song.
真巧... 我也想写歌...
Funny thing -- I also like to write mu--
菲尔
Phil?
我怎么了
What happened?
邓菲先生 你得了急性睾丸炎
Mr. Dunphy, you have acute orchitis.
睾丸大面积发炎
It's a massively inflamed testicle.
我在给你打抗生素点滴
I'm giving you an I.V. bag of antibiotics
也给你开了止痛药 因为...
and some pain meds because...
太惨了
Oh, boy.
真丢人
So embarrassed.
不敢相信我晕倒在摇滚巨星面前
I can't believe I passed out in front of a rock star.
请告诉我他不知道我晕倒的原因
Please tell me he didn't know why.
太棒了 你醒了
Oh, brilliant, you're awake.
我给你的蛋蛋拿了点冰来
I've got some ice for your biscuits.
不要啊 不 别别别
No. No, no, no, no, no!
太丢人了 咦 还真的...
Oh! Oh, that really --
还真的挺舒服的
Oh, that feels so good.
特里 能聊聊吗 拜托别不理我
Terry, can we talk? Please don't shut me out.
我知道我做错了
I know I messed up,
我对我午餐时的表现
and I'm so sorry for my...
非常抱歉[赖家王老五]
failure at lunch.
-先生 请坐下 -能让一个位置吗
- Sir, please sit down. - Do you mind?
不得换座
Same seats.
继续开庭
Let's proceed.
陪审员10号
Juror number 10,
你的家里
has anyone in your family
有没有人曾经是暴力犯罪的受害者
ever been the victim of a violent crime?
我的母亲...
Well...my mother...
-嘿 - 没叫你 你继续说
- Psst! - Not you, keep going.
对了
Oh, actually,
你能不能拍他肩膀叫他一下
could you tap him on the shoulder?
陪审员11号 这个男人是在骚扰你吗
Juror 11, is this man bothering you?
你是说这个影评人吗
You talking about the movie critic right here?
-当然了 他就是在骚扰我 -反对
- Absolutely, he's bothering me! - Objection!
我请求接近布拉德肖先生的许可
I request permission to approach Mr. Bradshaw.
不行 请求驳回
No! I mean, denied!
这不是你能请求的事情
Look, that's not a thing you can ask.
法官大人 我们想请陪审员3号离席
Your Honor, we'd like to dismiss Juror number 3.
什么 不不
What?! No, no.
我不会再这样了 我保证
I'll be good. I promise.
先生 现在请您离开
Sir, you have to leave now.
好吧
Fine.
我走
I'm going.
老兄 我会在停车场等着你的
I'll be waiting in the parking lot, buddy.
法官给我发了限制令
Judge hit me with a restraining order.
但泰瑞得签名
But Terry had to sign it.
我们会一起度过此劫的 菲利普
We're gonna get through this together, Phillip.
我不懂你为什么要在这里
I guess I just don't understand why you're here.
因为是你让我警醒
Well, because you really reached me back there,
我得做回个正常人
and I realized I got to be more of a regular guy.
邓菲 我有... 克里斯·马汀
Mr. Dunphy, I have your -- Chris Martin.
我是你的粉丝
Wow. I'm a huge fan.
-我能和你合个影吗 -不行
- Can I get a picture with you? - No.
是我想和你合影
I want a picture with you.
来吧
Come on.
开始
Let's do it.
菲尔 我有两千五百万粉丝
Phil, 25 million followers.
别了 谢谢你
No, thank you.
-我需要私人空间 -好啦
- Uh, I'd love some privacy. - All right.
还有空闲房间吗
Is there maybe a room opening up?
菲尔 亲爱的
Phil? Honey?
克里斯一打电话 我就赶来了
I came just as soon as Chris called me.
你好
Hello.
克莱尔 我不得不说
Claire, I've got to say, uh...
你比菲尔的照片里
You're even more beautiful
更漂亮
than you are in Phil's photos.
-我很喜欢你的音乐 -谢谢
- I like your music. - Well, thank you.
克莱尔 我能和你说几句话不
Claire, can I talk to you for one second.
当然啦 亲爱的
Yes, of course, sweetie, yes.
我希望克里斯·马汀离开
I want Chris Martin to leave.
什么 为什么
Hm? What? Why?
我这样子的时候 他在这里好奇怪
It's weird that he's here when I'm like this,
而且他把大家都吸引来了
and he's attracting attention.
我觉得不... 好吧
Oh, I don't think... yeah, okay.
克莱尔
Claire? Mm...
你可能不会喜欢这个
Oh, you're not gonna like this.
-太激动啦 -你邀请了你读书会的人吗
- This is so exciting! - You invited your book club?!
我们超喜欢你
We're huge fans.
读书会听起来很平民化
A book club sounds kind of regular.
我也应该加入一个
I should join one of those.
我们即将有空缺
There's about to be an opening in ours.
是我邀请你们来的
I'm the one who invited you here.
美丽的智慧女性们 你们都读什么呢
And what are you beautiful, uh, scholars reading?
《不知情的卡斯尔小姐》
"The Unwitting Miss Castle."
我喜欢这本书
Mm. I love that book.
但我觉得里面栅栏的比喻
Although I did find the fences metaphor
略俗
a little mundane.
-是啊 太做作了 -完全同意
- Oh, yes. Pretentious. - Completely agree.
上周我说了一模一样的话
I said the exact same thing last week,
你们却冲我翻白眼
and you guys just rolled your eyes at me.
克莱尔 别和德弗罗夫人似的
Claire, don't be such a Mrs. Devereaux.
-太像啦 太夸张了 -菲尔
- Twinsies! That is so you! - Hey, Phil.
我们照片有两万五千个赞啦
Our photo got 25,000 likes.
菲尔
Phil?
可能是因为药物的作用
Oh, it's probably all the meds.
放着我来
I'll handle this.
我曾和基思·理查兹去过狂欢节
I've been to Burning Man with Keith Richards.
不不 还是我来
No, no, no. I'll handle it.
我可是和我疯子妈一起度过假
I've been on vacation with my mother.
你要去哪呀 陌生人
Hey. Where are you off to, stranger?
亲爱的 我得一个人待会
Honey, I need to be alone.
亲爱的 对不起 我不该
Oh, honey, I'm sorry I invited
邀请读书会的姑娘们
the girls from book club.
我就是想让她们喜欢我
It's -- I just wanted them to like me.
我不敢相信这真的发生了
I can't believe this happened.
-这本应该是很棒的一天 -我知道
- This was supposed to be such an amazing day. - I know.
有没有什么我能做的
Is there anything I can do to make it better?
你可以让克里斯·马汀离开 就现在
Yes. You can make Chris Martin go away, now.
对不起 亲们
I'm so sorry, guys.
-我不是故意要引起 -不不不
- Oh, I didn't mean to cause a -- - Oh, no, no, no, no.
不是因为你这个人有问题
It's -- it's not you personally.
不不 就是我的问题 我老让别人分心
No, no, no, it is me. I'm a distraction.
每个人都想打招呼
Everyone wants to say "Hi"
或者合照
or they want to take a picture
或者睡我
or they want to sleep with me.
她们真的想
They sure do.
得了 玛丽
Shut 'er down, Marie.
简直是场噩梦
And it's a nightmare.
这开始影响到我的创造力
It's beginning to affect my creativity.
我写的最新一首歌是关于我的直升机
The last song I wrote was about my helicopter.
我实在没脸发行
I was too ashamed to release it.
我不得不卖给澳洲航空 卖了一百万
I had to sell it to Qantus for $1 million.
你的问题好枯苗望雨
Your problems are so sanguine.
这个词是这么用的吗
Is that how you use that word?
没人知道
Nobody knows.
总之 我希望我能做些什么
Oh, anyway, I wish there was something I could do
让这有所改善
to make this all better.
你可以买下那间房子
You could buy that house.
不 菲尔
No, Phil.
谢谢你 那是我过去的做法
Thanks to you, that's the old me.
好吧
Oh, good.
我知道你可以为他做什么
I know something you could do for him.
♪ 你一直寻找属于你的独特空间 ♪
♪ You've been looking for your own special space ♪
♪ 可称为栖息之所的地方 ♪
♪ Somewhere you can call your resting place ♪
♪ 你一直为了孩子和爱人寻找 ♪
♪ You've been looking for your kids and your spouse ♪
♪ 是时候给自己买套邓菲推荐的房子 ♪
♪ It's time time to buy yourself a Dunphy house ♪
♪ 邓菲 邓菲 邓菲 ♪
♪ Oh, Dunphy, Dunphy, Dunphy ♪
♪ 价格实惠又舒适 舒适 舒适 ♪
♪ They're affordable and comfy, comfy, comfy ♪
真不敢相信他能让这种歌好听
I can't believe he's actually making it work.
♪ 邓菲 邓菲 邓菲 ♪
♪ Oh, Dunphy, Dunphy, Dunphy ♪
那他为什么会不选我们
Why would he not pick us?
对啊 他想要的我们都有
Yeah, we gave him everything he wants --
能吵架 能和好
a fight, reconciliation...
而且我们上镜毫无压力
...not to mention we're camera-ready.
电视节目想要的全都符合
It's everything TV wants to be.
他还要我们怎么样啊
I mean, what does he want us to do,
帮他写好整集的脚本吗
write the episode for him?
美国民众应该有看我们得到小凉亭的机会
Yeah, America deserves to see us get a free gazebo.
他在那里
There he is.
我心里有5成想去跟他撕逼
I have half a mind to go over there and confront him.
我心里有另外5成
Yeah, well, I have the other half.
-等等 -你好
- Wait, wait. - Hi.
-不好意思 -有何能效劳吗
- Excuse us. - Can I help you guys?
给我们个解释如何
Yeah, how about an explanation.
你为什么不选我们上你节目
Why aren't you picking us for your show?
我们不够性感帅气吗
Yeah, what -- are we not sexy enough?
还是不够小鲜肉
Not young enough for your demo?
等等 难道是因为我们是同性恋吗
Wait, no, is it 'cause we're gay?
我好像没有看过同性恋情侣
You know, I've actually never seen a gay couple
上你的节目
on your little program.
也没看过体育老师兼副校长上过
Yeah, or a P.E. Teacher-slash-vice principal.
-他就是 -你就直说为何不选我们
- He's literally that. - Just tell us why you're not picking us.
两位 我已经没有节目了
Guys, I don't have a show anymore.
-少来 我们刚看完你... -对啊
- Please, we just saw that episode -- Yeah.
-上周圣安东尼奥市的小黛与小唐那集 -对啊
- Deb and Don in San Antonio last week? - Yeah.
小唐想要能烧烤的地方
Oh... Don wanted a place to grill.
-我们节目两年前就停了 -什么
- We got canceled, like, two years ago. - What?
-什么 -这节目不是很火吗
- What, why? - Yeah. It's such a popular show!
是这样的...
Look, uh...
电视台把我炒了
The network fired me...
-为什么 -他们发现我
- Why? - when they found out
建了一个网站让观众付费
that I had this website where people paid
看我裸体造东西
to watch me build stuff naked.
-是吗 -是啊
- Is that so? - Yeah.
裸到哪种程度
How naked?
非常
Very.
那你为什么还在
You know what, why are you hanging out
家居卖场里晃悠呢
in the aisles of a home store?
我在这里工作
I work here.
-还真是 -是啊
- You do. - Yeah.
-那如果你节目还在... -然后呢
- Hey, if you did still have a show, um... - Uh-huh?
你会请我们上吗
...would you pick us?
你说"愿意"不会死好吗
It costs you nothing to say "Yes."
天啊 我们又心灵相通了
Oh, my God, we agreed again.
我求过你别去了
I begged you not to go over there.
我现在好羞愧
I'm so embarrassed.
羞愧什么
Why?
他才是在哇哇哭的人
He's the one crying.
我最爱的部分就是
My favorite part was
看他边哭边想喘气时
when he was gasping for air between sobs,
那像小婴儿的样子
like a baby.
你看他 心都碎了
Look at him. He's broken.
万一他从此封笔了怎么办
What if he never writes again?
行 那我就去跟全世界剩下的
Okay, I'll apologize to the 12 people
12个还在看戏剧演出的人道歉
who still go out and watch plays.
你知道我也是戏剧专业的吧
You do know I'm a theater major, right?
是啊 所以当你哪天变成大编剧
Yes, and when you're a great play writer
然后也去到一家餐厅时
and you go to a restaurant --
前提是你下得起馆子
if you can afford it --
到时候你就得礼貌对待陌生粉丝
then you're gonna be nice to strangers,
因为这才是正确的待粉之道 懂了吗
because that's the right thing to do, okay?
抱歉 我不是有意要打扰
Excuse me. I don't mean to interrupt.
但我看到刚才发生的事了 我为你感到遗憾
But I saw what happened before, and I'm sorry about that.
但你挺身而出 去训了那贱人一顿
But the way you stood up to that jerk Anvilmaker
真的是大快人心
was kind of amazing, yeah.
为你点赞
Good for you.
小兄弟听我说
And young man, listen --
希望这能安慰到你
if this makes you feel any better,
其实他也那么对待我过
he did the same thing to me. Oh.
谢谢您的一番美言
That's very nice of you to say.
十分感谢您的鼓励
Thank you so much. So...
其实呢... 我也写作
You know, I, uh... I write.
要命
Oh, boy.
我不是那种... 那种...
No, it's not like I'm just some, you know, some --
过去一下 那种...
excuse me -- some --
那种乱吹牛逼的老滑头
you know, just some city slicker who --
毛都不懂就胡吹乱盖
who doesn't know what he's talking about.
但如果我能传授你一招
But, uh... if I could teach you one thing,
就这一招 如果你能学会
just one thing that you learn from this,
你的剧就能够变得活灵活现
it'll make your plays sound and look marvelous.
知道了吗
You know?
所以最重要的一件事就是...
So, the most important thing is to --
认识到创作其实就是改写
is to know that writing is really re-writing.
这句箴言你最好写下来
You may want to jot that down.
然后再"修改"
Uh... And then change it.
听出我这句话的哏了吗
Did you see what I did there?
抱歉 我们真的有事得先走了
You know what? We really need to be somewhere right now.
-对啊 别迟到了 -好的
- Yeah, we better go. - Okay.
-是啊 -没事
- Yeah. - All right.
谢谢你
Okay, thank you.
真的对不起 我之前没意识到我们多烦人
I'm sorry, we didn't realize we were so annoying.
是我们不对
Our bad.
祝下笔如神 势如破竹
Have fun storming the castle!
没回应
Nothing.
老子要去落发修面了
I'm gonna shave.
♪ 来感受那刺激 激 激 ♪
♪ Come feel the thrill, thrill, thrill ♪
♪ 的菲尔 尔 尔 ♪
♪ Of Phil, Phil, Phil ♪
♪ 那刺激 激 激 ♪
♪ The thrill, thrill, thrill ♪
♪ 菲尔的刺激 ♪
♪ The thrill of Phil ♪
能麻烦去把那声音关掉吗
Could you turn that down please?
大家一起来
Everybody.
我有几个小想法
So, a couple quick thoughts.